<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one or more
contributor license agreements. See the NOTICE file distributed with
this work for additional information regarding copyright ownership.
The ASF licenses this file to you under the Apache License, Version
2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance
with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 Unless required by
applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the
License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR
CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for
the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the
License.
-->
<section xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" version="5.0"
    xmlns:xl="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook ../../../content/dtd/docbook.xsd"
    xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook">
    <title>The Party Find help screen.</title>
    <para>The 'Find Party' is the default screen for the Party Manager application. It is used to locate existing
        parties. Various search criteria can be used, either based on the general party data
        like name role and type but also on the postal address, telephone (Telecom) and other like
        email address.</para>
    <para>If the find button is pressed, a list is presented containing several columns.</para>
    <para>The first column shows the Party ID. This is a string that uniquely identifies the Party in the system.</para>
    <para>The second column shows the Party logins. This is the string the user enters when logging into the system. A single Party can have more than one login. 
          In this case the &quot;(many)&quot; string is showed in place of the login string. The complete list of user logins can still be seen in the Party details screen.
          If a Party has no user login associated the string &quot;(none)&quot; is shown.</para>
    <para></para>
    <para></para>
    <para>In the &quot;Main Roletype&quot; column the role is listed which is a child of the &quot;Main role"&quot; roletype. It is currently set
        to &quot;Organisation&quot; and &quot;SFA Role&quot;. The later to be prepared to use he party in he SFA component. See the marketing application for more
        information</para>
</section>
