<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one or more
contributor license agreements. See the NOTICE file distributed with
this work for additional information regarding copyright ownership.
The ASF licenses this file to you under the Apache License, Version
2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance
with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 Unless required by
applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the
License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR
CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for
the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the
License.
-->
<section xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    version="5.0" xmlns:xl="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook ../../../content/dtd/docbook.xsd"
    xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook">
    <title>The Webtools Main page.</title>
    <para>
        This is the default screen for the Webtools application. Several links are present on this page to access specific tool screens directly. Using the application menu you can select the tool you need.       
    </para>
    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>The <link xl:href="">Logging</link> section is used to view and configure the OFBiz system logs.</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>The <link xl:href="">Cache &amp; Debug</link> section is used to monitor the OFBiz cache system status. You can even set or clear some cache content or force Garbage collection with this tool.</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>The <link xl:href="">Artifact Info</link> section is used to navigate through all OFBiz artifact files. When accessing this section the complete OFBiz code base is scanned and a list of all artifacts is offered to the user to be navigated.
        Please note that the initial scan can take a while to be completed.</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>The <link xl:href="">Entity Engine</link> section is used to interact with the entities defined in the system. You can view the entity structures, search for entity content, navigate though related entities, etc.</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>The <link xl:href="">Service Engine</link> section is used to interact with the services defined in the system. You can view all services details, monitor the jobs that are running, the active threads. You can even manually run a service or schedule a periodic/delaied job execution.</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>The <link xl:href="">Import/Export</link> section is used to transfer entity content from the OFBiz system to external systems and viceversa. Various import/export systems and formats are available.</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>The <link xl:href="">Configuration</link> section is used to set parameters for the OFBiz system.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
</section>
