<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one or more
contributor license agreements. See the NOTICE file distributed with
this work for additional information regarding copyright ownership.
The ASF licenses this file to you under the Apache License, Version
2.0 (the "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance
with the License. You may obtain a copy of the License at
http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0 Unless required by
applicable law or agreed to in writing, software distributed under the
License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR
CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied. See the License for
the specific language governing permissions and limitations under the
License.
-->
<section xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
    version="5.0" xmlns:xl="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
    xsi:schemaLocation="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook ../../../../applications/content/dtd/docbook.xsd"
    xmlns="http://docbook.org/ns/docbook">
  <title>The Example Main Help page.</title>
  <para>
    The Example application will allow you to discover the possibilities to create an application, with a lot of search boxes, lists and many more.</para>
  <para>This application could be used to have an example of the bests practices in user interface development in Apache - OFBiz.</para>
  <para>Look help for each example screen, help will explain which part of development is used in this case.</para>
  <para>For example, if you want to see how you should do to add some help you can look to help files in data/helpdata directory in example 
    component and data/ExempleHelpData.xml in content component.</para>

  <section>
    <title>Help file organization</title>
    <para>Help is managed by using content component functionality.</para>
    <para>Help can be for :
      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem><para>one component or sub-component, access is possible by navigation in help index tree and select it, contentId is associated to
          HELP_ROOT with contentAssocTypeId="TREE_CHILD" ;</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>one screen, access is done by help icon in screen (most of time on top), contentId is search on ContentAssoc.mapKey with 
          a value (helpTopic) build with component webSite and uri used to show this screen ;</para></listitem>
        <listitem><para>one portlet, access is done by a link on the portalPages (which contain this portlet) help, link is a showHelp (like 
          for a screen) with helpTopic build with "HELP_" and portletId</para></listitem>
       <listitem><para>one portal page, access is done by help icon if parameters.portalPageId is not empty, contentId is read on PortalPage
          (or originalPortalPage if exist) and is show on top of portlet list contain on it.</para></listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </para>
  </section>

  <section>
    <title>Development help sub-subject</title>
    <para>To have the complete list you should click on index button and look to example tree option, but here is a list of
      main shortcut :
      <itemizedlist>
        <listitem><para>How is organize <link xl:href="showHelp?helpTopic=DOCUMENTATION_SYSTEM">The Apache OFBiz documentation system</link></para></listitem>
        <listitem><para><link xl:href="showHelp?helpTopic=EXAMPLE_docbook">What it's possible to do in help file</link></para></listitem>
      </itemizedlist>
    </para>
  </section>
</section>
