<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--

    Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one
    or more contributor license agreements.  See the NOTICE file
    distributed with this work for additional information
    regarding copyright ownership.  The ASF licenses this file
    to you under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the
    "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance
    with the License.  You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing,
    software distributed under the License is distributed on an
    "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY
    KIND, either express or implied.  See the License for the
    specific language governing permissions and limitations
    under the License.
-->
<resource xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://ofbiz.apache.org/dtds/ofbiz-properties.xsd">
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.ASSETMAINTADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Asset Maintenance Admin group, has all maintenance permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo permesso manutenzione cespiti, ha tutti i permessi di manutenzione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">資産メンテナンス管理グループは、すべてのメンテナンス権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">资产维护管理组，具有全部维护权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">資產維護管理群組,具有全部維護權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.ASSETMAINTTECH">
        <value xml:lang="en">Asset Maintenance Technician group, has view and update.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo permesso manutenzione tecnica cespiti, ha i permessi di visualizzazione e aggiornamento.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">資産メンテナンス技術グループは、表示および更新権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">资产维护技术人员组，具有浏览和更新权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">資產維護技術人員群組,具有檢視和更新權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.BIZADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Full Business Applications permission group, has all business app admin permissions, not technical permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Permisos completos para las Aplicaciones de Negocio, no posee permisos técnicos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe à autorisation complète sur les applications de gestion : ayant toutes les autorisations d'administration des application de gestion, sans autorisations techniques.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo permesso applicazioni full busines, hai tutti i permessi amministratore sulle applicazioni, nessun permesso tecnico.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">全業務権限グループは、すべての業務管理権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Полная группа прав 'Деловые приложения', содержит все права для администрирования деловых приложений, нет технических прав.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">全部商业应用程序权限组，具有全部商业应用程序管理权限，不是技术人员权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">全部商業應用程式權限群組,具有全部商業應用程式管理權限,不是技術人員權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.CATALOGADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Catalog Admin group, has all catalog permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Administrador del Catálogo, tiene todos los permisos de Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration de catalogue, ayant toutes les autorisations sur le catalogue</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore catalogo, ha tutti i permessi catalogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理グループは、すべてのカタログ権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Группа 'Администратор каталога', содержит все права на каталог.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">กลุ่มผู้ดูแลระบบหมวดหมู่, มีการอนุญาตหมวดหมู่ทั้งหมด.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理组，具有全部目录权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理群組,具有全部型錄權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.CATALOGADMIN_LTD">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Catalog Admin group, has limited catalog permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Administrador Limitado del Catálogo, tiene permisos limitados de Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration limitée de catalogue, ayant des autorisations limitées sur le catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo limitato amministratore catalogo, ha limitati permessi catalogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">限定カタログ管理グループは、限定されたカタログ権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Группа 'Ограниченный администратор каталога', содержит ограниченные права на каталог.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">กลุ่มผู้ดูแลระบบหมวดหมู่จำกัด, มีการอนุญาตหมวดหมู่จำกัด.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">有限的目录管理组，具有有限的目录权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">有限的型錄管理群組,具有有限的型錄權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.COMPDOCADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">CompDoc admin group, all permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo permesso amministratore composizione documenti, ha tutti permessi di manutenzione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">複合文書管理グループは、すべての権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">合成文档管理组，全部权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">複合檔管理群組,全部權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.CONTENT_USER">
        <value xml:lang="en">Content user group; all limited content permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Grupo de usuarios de contenidos; todos los permisos de contenido limitados</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'utilisateurs de contenu, toutes autorisations de contenu limitées.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo utenti contenuto; ha tutti i permessi limitati ai contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツユーザグループは、限定されたコンテンツ権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容用户组；全部有限的内容权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容使用者群組;全部有限的內容權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.FLEXADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Flexible Admin group, has all granular permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Permisos de Administración Flexible, posee todos los permisos granulares.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration flexible, ayant toutes les autorisations définies de manière granulaire.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore flessibile, ha tutti i permessi specificati.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">フレキシブル管理グループは、すべての粒度の権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Группа 'Гибкий администратор', содержит все гранулированные права.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">Flexible Admin group, has all granular permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">缓存管理组，具有全部颗粒的权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">快取管理群組,具有全部顆粒的權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.FULLADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Full Admin group, has all general permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Permisos de Administración Completos, posee todos los permisos generales.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration totale, ayant toutes les autorisations.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore completo, ha tutti i permessi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">フル管理グループは、すべての全般の権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Группа 'Полный администратор', содержит все общие права.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">Full Admin group, has all general permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">完全管理组，具有全部通用权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">完全管理群組,具有全部通用權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.MYPORTAL_CUSTOMER">
        <value xml:lang="en">Customer user of MYPORTAL, Limited access to own custRequests, and project</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Utente di myportal, accesso limitato al proprietario delle richieste cliente, e progetti</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">私のポータルの顧客ユーザは、自分の顧客リクエストおよびプロジェクトに限定されたアクセスができます。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">我的门户客户用户，受限访问自己的客户请求，以及项目</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">我的入口網站客戶使用者,受限於訪問自己的客戶請求,以及專案</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.MYPORTAL_EMPL-NOEML">
        <value xml:lang="en">Employee user of MYPORTAL, Limited access to the projectmgr and comms, custReq, no email</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Utente impiegato di myportal, accesso limitato ai progetti e comunicazioni, richieste cliente, no email</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">私のポータルの従業員ユーザは、プロジェクト管理、通信、顧客リクエスト、Eメール無に限定されたアクセスができます。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">我的门户雇员用户，受限访问项目管理以及沟通、客户请求，不包括电子邮件</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">我的入口員工使用者,受限於訪問專案管理以及通訊、客戶請求,不包括電子郵件</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.MYPORTAL_EMPLOYEE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Employee user of myportal, Limited access to the projectmgr, comms,custRequests</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Utente impiegato di myportal, accesso limitato ai progetti e comunicazioni, richieste cliente</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">私のポータルの従業員ユーザは、プロジェクト管理、通信、顧客リクエストに限定されたアクセスができます。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">我的门户雇员用户，受限访问项目管理、沟通、客户请求</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">我的入口員工使用者,受限訪問專案管理、通訊、客戶請求</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.ORDERADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Order Admin group, has all order permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Administrador de Órdenes, tiene todos los permisos de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration des commandes, ayant toutes les autorisations  sur les commandes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore ordini, ha tutti i permessi ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理グループは、すべての注文権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Группа 'Администратор заказов', содержит все права на заказ.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">คำสั่งซื้อสินค้าของกลุ่มผู้ดูแลระบบ, มีการอนุญาตคำสั่งซื้อสินค้าทั้งหมด.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理组，具有全部订单权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理群組,具有全部訂單權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.ORDERADMIN_LTD">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Order Admin group, has all limited order permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Administrador Limitado de Órdenes, tiene permisos limitados de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration limité, ayant toutes les autorisations limitées sur les commandes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore limitato ordini, ha tutti i permessi limitati ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">限定注文管理グループは、すべての限定された注文権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Группа 'Ограниченный администратор заказов', содержит все ограниченные права на заказ.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">คำสั่งซื้อสินค้าจำกัดของกลุ่มผู้ดูแลระบบ, มีการอนุญาตคำสั่งซื้อสินค้าจำกัดทั้งหมด.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">受限的订单管理组，具有全部受限的订单权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">受限的訂單管理群組,具有全部受限的訂單權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.ORDERENTRY">
        <value xml:lang="en">Order Entry Admin group; permissions for creating orders.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Administrador de Entrada de Órdenes, tiene permisos para crear Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration de saisie de commande,  autorisations pour créer des commandes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore inserimento ordini, ha tutti i permessi per creare ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文エントリ管理グループは、注文を作成する権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Грппа 'Администратор ввода заказов'; права для создания заказов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">กลุ่มผู้ดูแลระบบกรอกข้อมูลคำสั่งซื้อสินค้า ; การอนุญาตสำหรับการสร้างคำสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单记录管理组；创建订单权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單記錄管理群組;新建訂單權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.ORDERENTRY_ALL">
        <value xml:lang="en">Order entry permission for all stores. No special role is needed.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Permisos para entrada de Órdenes para todas las tiendas. No es necesario un rol especial.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Autorisation de saisie de commande pour tous les centres de profit.  Aucun rôle spécial n'est nécessaire.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore inserimento ordini per tutti i negozi, nessun ruolo è necessario.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">すべての店舗の注文をエントリする権限。特別なロールは必要ありません。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Права на ввод заказов для всех торговых точек. Специальные роли не требуются.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การอนุญาตการกรอกข้อมูลคำสั่งซื้อสินค้าสำหรับคลังทั้งหมด. ไม่มีสถานะพิเศษที่ต้องการ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">全部店铺的订单记录管理组。不需要特别的角色。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">全部商店的訂單輸入管理群組.不需要特別的角色.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.ORDERPROC">
        <value xml:lang="en">Admin group for restricted order processing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Administrador para procesamiento de Órdenes restringido.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration pour le traitement restreint de commande.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore con permessi ridotti all'avanzamento ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文処理に制限された管理グループ。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Административная группа для ограниченной обработки заказов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">กลุ่มผู้ดูแลระบบสำหรับจำกัดการประมวลผลคำสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">管理组用于受限制的订单流程。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">管理群組用於受限制的訂單流程.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.ORDERPURCH">
        <value xml:lang="en">Order entry with purchasing permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Entrada de Órdenes con permisos de compra.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Saisie de commande avec autorisations d'achat.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Inserimento ordini con permessi acquisto ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">購買の注文エントリ権限</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ввод заказов с правами на закупку.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การกรอกข้อมูลคำสั่งซื้อสินค้าด้วยการอนุญาตการสั่งซื้อ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">具有采购权限的订单记录。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">具有訂單輸入的採購權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.ORDERSUPPLIER_LTD">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Order Admin group for Supplier Agents.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Administrador Limitado de Órdenes para Agentes Proveedores.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration de commande limitée pour les  fournisseurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore ordini limitato per agenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サプライやエージェントの限定された注文管理グループ。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Группа 'Ограниченный администратор заказов' для Агентов поставщика.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">คำสั่งซื้อสินค้าจำกัดขงกลุ่มผู้ดูแลระบบสำหรับตัวแทนผู้จัดหาสิ่งของ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">有限的订单管理组用于供货商。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">有限的訂單管理群組用於供應商.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.PARTYADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Party Admin group, has all party permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Administrador de Entidades, tiene todos los permisos de Entidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration d'acteur, ayant toutes les autorisations sur les acteurs.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore soggetti, ha tutti i permessi soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理グループは、すべての取引先権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Группа 'Администратор участников', содержит все права на участников.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">กลุ่มผู้ใช้กลุ่มผู้ดูแลระบบ , มีการอนุญาตกลุ่มผู้ใช้ทั้งหมด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理组，具有全部会员权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理群組,具有全部團體權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.PROJECTADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Project Admin group, has update access to own projects.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo permesso amministrazione progetti, ha accesso in aggiornamento come proprietario progetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">プロジェクト管理グループは、自分のプロジェクトを更新アクセスすることができます。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">项目管理组，具有对自己项目的更新权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">專案管理群組,具有對自己專案的更新權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.PROJECTUSER">
        <value xml:lang="en">Project User group, has read, task create/assign and timesheet create/update access to own projects.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo permesso utente progetti, può leggere, creare/assegnare compiti e creare/aggiornare timbrature accedere ai propri progetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">プロジェクトユーザグループは、自分のプロジェクにタスクを作成/割当、および予定表を作成/更新アクセスすることができます。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">项目用户组，具有对自己项目的读、任务创建/指派以及工单创建/更新权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">專案使用者群組,具有對自己專案的讀、任務新建/指派以及工時表新建/更新權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.SECURITYADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Security Admin group, has all permissions to modify security settings in party manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Grupo de administradores de seguridad, tiene todos los permisos para modificar ajustes de seguridad en el gestor de participantes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration de sécurité, ayant toutes les autorisations pour modifier les paramètres de sécurité dans la gestion d'acteur.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore sicurezza, ha tutti i permessi per modificare le impostazioni sicurezza nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">セキュリティ管理グループは、取引先管理ですべてのセキュリティ設定を更新する権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">安全管理组，具有在会员管理中修改安全设置的全部权限</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">安全管理群組,具有在團體管理中修改安全設定的全部權限</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.VIEWADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Demo Admin group, has all view permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Demo de Administración, tiene todos los permisos de visualización.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'administration de démonstration, ayant toutes les autorisations de visualisation.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo amministratore demo, ha tutti i permessi in visualizzazione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">デモ管理グループは、すべての表示権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Группа 'Демо администратор', содержит все права на просмотр.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ตัวอย่างกลุ่มผู้ดูแลระบบ, มีการอนุญาตการแสดงทั้งหมด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">演示管理组，具有全部浏览权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">Demo管理群組,具有全部檢視權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityGroup.description.WORKEFFORT_USER">
        <value xml:lang="en">WorkEffort user group; all limited workeffort permissions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Grupo de usuarios de esfuerzos de trabajo; todos los permisos de esfuerzo de trabajo limitados</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Groupe d'utilisateurs des tâches, toutes autorisations limitées sur les tâches.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gruppo utente impiegno di lavoro, ha tutti i permessi limitati agli impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果ユーザグループは、限定された作業成果権限があります。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务用户组；全部受限的人工服务权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入服務使用者群組;全部受限的工作投入服務權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission description.ENTITY_SYNC_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the Entity Sync Admin pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Usar las páginas de Administración de Sincronización de Entidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Utiliser les pages d'administration de synchronisation d'entités.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Usare le pagine di amministrazione per la sincronizzazione dei dati.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">エンティティ同期管理ページの使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Использование страниц Администрирование синхронизации сущностей.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">Use the Entity Sync Admin pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">使用实体同步管理页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">使用資料實體同步管理頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission description.EXAMPLE_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en las pantallas de Administración de Ejemplo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES les opérations dans les écrans d'exemples.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella gestione degli Esempio.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление примерами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในหน้าจอการจัดการตัวอย่าง</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在样例管理页面中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission description.EXAMPLE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en las pantallas de Administración de Ejemplo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création dans les écrans d'exemples</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione Esempi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Управление примерами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในหน้าจอการจัดการตัวอย่าง</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在样例管理页面中创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission description.EXAMPLE_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en las pantallas de Administración de Ejemplo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression dans les écrans d'exemples.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione Esempi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Управление примерами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในหน้าจอการจัดการตัวอย่าง</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在样例管理页面中删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission description.EXAMPLE_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en las pantallas de Administración de Ejemplo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de mise à jour dans les écrans d'exemples.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione Esempi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Управление примерами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทการทำงานในหน้าจอการจัดการตัวอย่าง</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在样例管理页面中更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission description.EXAMPLE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en las pantallas de Administración de Ejemplo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Voir les opérations dans les écrans d'exemples.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione Esempi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление примерами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงการทำงานในหน้าจอการจัดการตัวอย่าง</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在样例管理页面中浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCOUNTING_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Accounting Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Administrador de Contabilidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES les opérations dans la gestion de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella gestione della contabilità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">会計管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление учетом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการจัดการบัญชี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在财务管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在會計管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCOUNTING_COMM_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View commission rates.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Ver tasas de comisión.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Voir les taux de commission.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione percentuali commissioni.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">委託レートを表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Просмотр ставок комиссионных.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงอัตราค่าคอมมิชชัน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">浏览佣金比例。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視佣金比例.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCOUNTING_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Accounting Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Administrador de Contabilidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création dans la gestion de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione della contabilità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">会計管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Управление учетом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในการจัดการบัญชี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在财务管理中创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在會計管理中新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCOUNTING_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Accounting Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Administrador de Contabilidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression dans la gestion de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione della contabilità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">会計管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Управление учетом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในการจัดการบัญชี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在财务管理中删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在會計管理中刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCOUNTING_PRINT_CHECKS">
        <value xml:lang="en">Print checks.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Imprimir cheques.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Imprimer les chèques.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Stampa degli assegni.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">小切手を印刷。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Печать чеков.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ตรวจสอบการพิมพ์</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">打印支票。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">列印支票.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCOUNTING_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Accounting Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en el Administrador de Contabilidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Metre à jour les opérations dans la gestion de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione della contabilità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">会計管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Управление учетом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการบัญชี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在财务管理中更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在會計管理中更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCOUNTING_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Accounting Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Administrador de Contabilidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Voir les opérations dans la gestion de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione della contabilità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">会計管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление учетом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงการทำงานในการจัดการบัญชี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">财务管理中浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">會計管理中檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_ATX_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations involving general ledger accounting transactions and entries.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni che coinvolgono transazioni e voci di contabilità</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">総勘定元帳会計仕訳およびエントリに関するすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">涉及总账账户交易和记录的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">涉及總帳帳戶交易和記錄的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_ATX_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create general ledger accounting transaction and entries.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Creación de transacciones y entradas de contabilidad de libro mayor.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer les transactions et entrées du registre général de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creazione delle transazioni nella contabilità generale.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">総勘定元帳会計仕訳およびエントリの作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание проводок и занесений главной книги.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างรายการบัญชีแยกประเภททั่วไปและสิทธิในการเข้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">创建总账账户交易和记录。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">新建總帳帳戶交易和記錄.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_ATX_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete general ledger accounting transaction and entries.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Eliminar transacciones y entradas de contabilidad de libro mayor.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Supprimer les transactions et entrées du registre général de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Eliminare le transazioni nella contabilità generale.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">総勘定元帳会計仕訳およびエントリの削除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Удаление проводок и занесений главной книги.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบรายการบัญชีแยกประเภททั่วไปและสิทธิในการเข้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">删除总账账户交易和记录。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">刪除總帳帳戶交易和記錄.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_ATX_POST">
        <value xml:lang="en">Post general ledger accounting transactions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Publicar transacciones de contabilidad de libro mayor.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Publier les transactions du registre général de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Contabilizzare le transazioni nella contabilità generale.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">総勘定元帳会計仕訳の転記。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Использование бухгалтерских проводок главной книги.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ประกาศรายการบัญชีแยกประเภททั่วไป</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">过账总账账户交易和记录。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">過帳總帳帳戶交易和記錄.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_ATX_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update general ledger accounting transaction and entries.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualizar transacciones y entradas de contabilidad de libro mayor.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mettre à jour les transactions du registre général de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare le transazioni nella contabilità generale.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">総勘定元帳会計仕訳およびエントリの更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление проводок и занесений главной книги.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทรายการบัญชีแยกประเภททั่วไปและสิทธิในการเข้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">更新总账账户交易和记录。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">更新總帳帳戶交易和記錄.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_ATX_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View general ledger accounting transaction and entries.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Visualizzare le transazioni nella contabilità generale.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">総勘定元帳会計仕訳およびエントリの表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">浏览总账账户交易和记录。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視總帳帳戶交易和記錄.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_FX_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Set foreign exchange rates.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Establecer tasas de cambio de divisa.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Fixer les taux de devises étrangères.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Impostare i valori cambio valuta.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">外国為替レートの設定。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Устанавливать курсы иностранных валют.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">กำหนดอัตราการปริวรรตเงินตรา</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">设置外汇汇率。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">設置外匯匯率.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_PREF_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL organization accounting preferences operations</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nelle preferenze di contabilità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">すべての組織会計設定操作</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">所有机构账户设置操作</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">所有機構帳戶偏好操作</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_PREF_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Set organization accounting preferences.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Establecer preferencias contables de la organización.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Définir les préférences d'organisation de comptabilité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Impostare le preferenze di contabilità per l'organizzazione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">組織会計設定の設定</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Устанавливать учетные параметры организации.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">กำหนดสิทธิพิเศษให้บัญชีขององค์กร</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">设置机构账户设置</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">偏好機構帳戶偏好</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_PREF_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete organization accounting preferences</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nelle preferenze di contabilità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">組織会計設定の削除</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">删除机构账户设置</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">刪除機構帳戶偏好</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_PREF_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update organization accounting preferences</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nelle preferenze di contabilità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">組織会計設定の更新</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">更新机构账户设置</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">更新機構帳戶偏好</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ACCTG_PREF_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View organization accounting preferences</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nelle preferenze di contabilità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">組織会計設定の表示</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">浏览机构账户设置</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視機構帳戶偏好</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ARTIFACT_INFO_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View the Artifact Info pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione pagine informazioni artifatti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">成果物情報ページの表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">浏览人工制品信息页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視人造物品資訊頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ASSETMAINT_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL Asset Maintenance operations.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni per la gestione cespiti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">すべての資産管理操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">全部资产维护操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">全部資產維護操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ASSETMAINT_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Asset Maintenance Create operations.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione per la gestione cespiti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">資産管理作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">资产维护创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">資產維護新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ASSETMAINT_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Asset Maintenance Delete operations.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione per la gestione cespiti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">資産管理削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">资产维护删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">資產維護刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ASSETMAINT_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Asset Maintenance Update operations.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento per la gestione cespiti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">資産管理更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">资产维护更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">資產維護更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ASSETMAINT_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Asset Maintenance View permission.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione per la gestione cespiti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">資産管理表示権限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">资产维护浏览权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">資產維護檢視權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Administrador del Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES opérations en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella gestione cataloghi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการจัดการหมวดหมู่</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Administrador del Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione cataloghi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในการจัดการหมวดหมู่</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Administrador del Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione cataloghi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในการจัดการหมวดหมู่</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_PRICE_MAINT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Permission required, in addition to other applicable permissions, to maintain product prices, promotions, and price rules.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Se requiere un permiso, además de otros permisos aplicables, para mantener la información de precios de productos incluyendo, precios, promociones y reglas de precios.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Autorisation exigée, en plus d'autres autorisations applicables, pour mettre à jour l'information sur les prix de produit, comprenant des prix, des promotions, et des règles de prix.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Permesso richiesto, in aggiunya agli altri permessi applicabili, per manutenere le informazioni sui prezzi prodotti, promozioni, e regole prezzi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">製品価格、プロモーション、および価格ルールを管理するために必要な、その他追加で適用される権限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Дополнительные права для редактирования ценовой информации, включая цены, акции и правила ценообразования.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ต้องการการอนุญาต, ในการเพิ่มถึงการอนุญาตการปฏิบัติอื่น ๆ, ถึงการรักษาราคาสินค้าข้อมูลการรวมราคา,โปรโมชัน,และข้อบังคับราคา</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">需要权限，除了其它可用的权限，还要能维护产品价格、促销和价格规则。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">需要權限,除了其他可用的權限,還要能維護產品價格、促銷和價格規則.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_PURCHASE_ALLOW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Allow create/update of 'Purchase Allow' in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Permetti la creazione/aggiornamento di gestione cataloghi di 'Permetti acquisto'.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理で'購入可能'の作成/更新を許可。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中“允许采购”的允许创建/更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中『允許採購』的允許新建/更新.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_ROLE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Create operations in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación Limitadas en el Administrador del Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création limitée en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione limitata nella gestione cataloghi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理で限定された作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ограниченные права на операции создания в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการสร้างการทำงานในการจัดการหมวดหมู่</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中有限的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中有限的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_ROLE_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Delete operations in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación Limitadas en el Administrador del Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression limitée en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione limitata nella gestione cataloghi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理で限定された削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ограниченные права на операции удаления в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการลบการทำงานในการจัดการหมวดหมู่</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中有限的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中有限的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_ROLE_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Update operations in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización Limitadas en el Administrador del Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de mise à jour limitée en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento limitata nella gestione cataloghi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理で限定された更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ограниченные права на операции обновления в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการอัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการหมวดหมู่</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中有限的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中有限的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en el Administrador del Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de mise à jour en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione cataloghi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การอัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการหมวดหมู่</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Administrador del Catálogo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione cataloghi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การแสดงการทำงานในการจัดการหมวดหมู่</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CATALOG_VIEW_ALLOW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Allow create/update of 'View Allow' in the Catalog Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Permetti la creazione/aggiornamento di gestione cataloghi di 'Visualizzazione permessa'.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">カタログ管理で'表示可能'の作成/更新を許可。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">目录管理中“允许浏览”的允许创建/更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">型錄管理中『允許檢視』的允許新建/更新.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.COMMON_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Common Component.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nel componente Common.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">共通コンポーネントで作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">通用组件中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">通用元件中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.COMMON_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Common Component.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nel componente Common.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">共通コンポーネントで削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">通用组件中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">共用元件中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.COMMON_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Common Component.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nel componente Common.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">共通コンポーネントで更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">通用组件中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">共用元件中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.COMMON_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Common Component.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nel componente Common.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">共通コンポーネントで表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">通用组件中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">通用元件中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CONTENTMGR_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Content Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Administrador de Contenido.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES les opérations en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella gestione contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツ管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление контентом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการจัดการหัวข้อ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CONTENTMGR_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Content Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Administrador de Contenido.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Création d'opérations en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツ管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การสร้างการทำงานในการจัดการหัวข้อ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容管理中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容管理中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CONTENTMGR_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Content Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Administrador de Contenido.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Suppression d'opérations en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツ管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การลบการทำงานในการจัดการหัวข้อ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容管理中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容管理中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CONTENTMGR_ROLE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Create operations in the Content Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni limitate di creazione nella gestione contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツ管理での限定された作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容管理中有限的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容管理中有限的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CONTENTMGR_ROLE_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Delete operations in the Content Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni limitate di cancellazione nella gestione contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツ管理での限定された削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容管理中有限的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容管理中有限的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CONTENTMGR_ROLE_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Update operations in the Content Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni limitate di aggiornamento nella gestione contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツ管理での限定された更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容管理中有限的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容管理中有限的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CONTENTMGR_ROLE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited View operations in the Content Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni limitate di visualizzazione nella gestione contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツ管理での限定された表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容管理中有限的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容管理中有限的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CONTENTMGR_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Content Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en el Administrador de Contenido.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mise à jour d'opérations en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツ管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การอัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการหัวข้อ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容管理中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容管理中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.CONTENTMGR_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Content Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Administrador de Contenido.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Visualisation d'opérations en gestion de catalogue.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione contenuti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コンテンツ管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление каталогом продуктов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การแสดงการทำงานในการจัดการหัวข้อ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">内容管理中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">內容管理中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.DATAFILE_MAINT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the Data File Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Usar las páginas de Mantenimiento de Archivos de Datos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Utiliser les pages de maintenance du fichier de données.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Usare le pagine di gestione file dati.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">データファイル管理ページの使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Использование страниц Обслуживание файлов данных.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ใช้ไฟล์ข้อมูลในหน้าการบำรุงรักษา</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">使用数据文件维护页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">使用資料檔維護頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.EBAY_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the eBay application.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nell'applicazione eBay.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">eBay業務での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">EBay应用程序中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">eBay應用程式中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ENTITY_DATA_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL with the Entity Data Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODO dentro de las páginas de Mantenimiento de Datos de Entidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUT avec les pages de maintenance des données d'entité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le pagine nella gestione dei dati entità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">エンティティデータ管理ページでのすべて。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все права для страниц Обслуживание файлов данных.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ทั้งหมดด้วยหน้าการบำรุงรักษาข้อมูลเอนทิตี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">全部具有实体数据维护的页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">全部具有資料實體資料維護的頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ENTITY_DATA_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create with the Entity Data Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Creación con las páginas de Mantenimiento de Datos de Entidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer avec les pages de maintenance des données d'entité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Pagine per creare dati entità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">エンティティデータ管理ページでの作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание для страниц Обслуживание данных сущностей.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างด้วยหน้าการบำรุงรักษาข้อมูลเอนทิตี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">具有实体数据维护页面的创建。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">具有資料實體資料維護頁面的新建.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ENTITY_DATA_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete with the Entity Data Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Eliminación con las páginas de Mantenimiento de Datos de Entidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Supprimer avec les pages de maintenance des données d'entité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Pagine per eliminare dati entità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">エンティティデータ管理ページでの削除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Удаление для страниц Обслуживание данных сущностей.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบด้วยหน้าการบำรุงรักษาข้อมูลเอนทิตี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">具有实体数据维护页面的删除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">具有資料實體資料維護頁面的刪除.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ENTITY_DATA_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update with the Entity Data Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualización con las páginas de Mantenimiento de Datos de Entidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mettre à jour avec les pages de maintenance des données d'entité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Pagine per aggiornare dati entità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">エンティティデータ管理ページでの更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление для страниц Обслуживание данных сущностей.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทด้วยหน้าการบำรุงรักษาข้อมูลเอนทิตี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">具有实体数据维护页面的更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">具有資料實體資料維護頁面的更新.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ENTITY_DATA_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View with the Entity Data Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Visualización con las páginas de Mantenimiento de Datos de Entidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Visualiser avec les pages de maintenance des données d'entité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Pagine per visualizzare dati entità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">エンティティデータ管理ページでの表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Просмотр для страниц  Обслуживание данных сущностей.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงด้วยหน้าการบำรุงรักษาข้อมูลเอนทิตี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">具有实体数据维护页面的浏览。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">具有資料實體資料維護頁面的檢視.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ENTITY_MAINT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the Entity Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Usar las páginas de Mantenimiento de Datos de Entidad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Utiliser les pages de maintenance d'entité.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Pagine per gestire le entità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">エンティティ管理ページの使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Использование страниц Обслуживание данных сущностей.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ใช้หน้าการรักษาสภาพเอนทิตี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">使用实体数据维护页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">使用資料實體資料維護頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ENTITY_SYNC_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the Entity Sync Admin pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Usare le pagine di amministrazione sincronizzazione entità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">エンティティ同期管理ページの使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">使用实体同步管理页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">使用資料實體同步管理頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ENUM_STATUS_MAINT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the Enum and Status Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Usar las páginas de Mantenimiento de Enumeraciones y Estados.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Utiliser les pages de maintenance de statut et énumération.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Pagine per gestire enumerazioni e stati.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">列挙およびステータス管理ページの使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Использование страниц Обслуживание перечеслений и статусов.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">Use the Enum and Status Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">使用枚举和状态维护页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">使用列舉和狀態維護頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.EXAMPLE_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni di gestione esempi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">样例管理屏中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.EXAMPLE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione esempi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">样例管理屏中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.EXAMPLE_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione esempi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">样例管理屏中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.EXAMPLE_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione esempi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">样例管理屏中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.EXAMPLE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Example Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione esempi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サンプル管理画面での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">样例管理屏中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在範例管理畫面中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.FACILITY_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Facility Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Administrador de Establecimientos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES opérations en gestion d'entreposage.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le pagine nella gestione stabilimenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">拠点管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление объектами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการจัดการคลังสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">场所管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">場所管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.FACILITY_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Facility Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Administrador de Establecimientos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création en gestion d'entreposage.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione stabilimenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">拠点管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Управление объектами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในการจัดการคลังสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">场所管理中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">場所管理中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.FACILITY_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Facility Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Administrador de Establecimientos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression en gestion d'entreposage.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione stabilimenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">拠点管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Управление объектами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในการจัดการคลังสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">场所管理中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">場所管理中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.FACILITY_ROLE_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited update operations in the Facility Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización Limitadas en el Administrador de Establecimientos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de mise à jour limitée en gestion d'entreposage.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento limitate nella gestione stabilimenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">拠点管理での限定された更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции ограниченного обновления в приложении Управление объектами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการอัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการคลังสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">场所管理中有限的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">場所管理中有限的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.FACILITY_ROLE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited view operations in the Facility Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización Limitada en el Administrador de Establecimientos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation limitée en gestion d'entreposage.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione limitate nella gestione stabilimenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">拠点管理での限定された表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции ограниченного просмотра в Управление объектами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการแสดงการทำงานในการจัดการคลังสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">场所管理中有限的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">場所管理中有限的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.FACILITY_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Facility Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en el Administrador de Establecimientos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations d'actualisation en gestion d'entreposage.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione stabilimenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">拠点管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Управление объектами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การอัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการคลังสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">场所管理中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">場所管理中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.FACILITY_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Facility Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Administrador de Establecimientos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation en gestion d'entreposage.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione stabilimenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">拠点管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление объектами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การแสดงการทำงานในการจัดการคลังสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">场所管理中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">場所管理中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.HUMANRES_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the HumanRes Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione risorse umane.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">人事管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人力资源管理中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">人力資源管理中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.HUMANRES_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the HumanRes Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione risorse umane.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">人事管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人力资源管理中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">人力資源管理中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.HUMANRES_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the HumanRes Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione risorse umane.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">人事管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人力资源管理中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">人力資源管理中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.HUMANRES_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the HumanRes Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione risorse umane.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">人事管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人力资源管理中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">人力資源管理中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.LABEL_MANAGER_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View the Labels Info pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione pagine per gestione labels.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ラベル情報ページの表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">浏览标签信息页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視標簽資訊頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MANUAL_PAYMENT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Manual Payment Transaction.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Pago Manual de Transacciones.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Transaction de paiement manuel.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Transazioni manuali pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">手動支払トランザクション。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ручная проводка платежа.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">รายการการชำระเงินด้วยมือ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">手工支付交易。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">手動付款交易.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MANUFACTURING_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Manufacturing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Administrador de Producción.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Toutes les opérations en gestion de fabrication.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le pagine nella gestione produzione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">生産管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление производством.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการจัดการการผลิต</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">制造管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">製造管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MANUFACTURING_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Manufacturing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Administrador de Producción.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création en gestion de fabrication.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione produzione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">生産管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении  Управление производством.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในการจัดการการผลิต</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">制造管理中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">製造管理中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MANUFACTURING_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Manufacturing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Administrador de Producción.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression en gestion de fabrication.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione produzione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">生産管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении  Управление производством.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในการจัดการการผลิต</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">制造管理中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">製造管理中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MANUFACTURING_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Manufacturing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en el Administrador de Producción.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations d'actualisation en gestion de fabrication.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione produzione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">生産管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении  Управление производством.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การอัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการการผลิต</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">制造管理中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">製造管理中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MANUFACTURING_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Manufacturing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Administrador de Producción.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation en gestion de fabrication.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione produzione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">生産管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление производством.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การแสดงการทำงานในการจัดการการผลิต</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">制造管理中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">製造管理中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MARKETING_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Marketing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Administrador de Marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Toutes les opérations en gestion de marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le pagine nella gestione vendite.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">マーケティング管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление маркетингом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการจัดการการตลาด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">市场管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">行銷管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MARKETING_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Marketing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Administrador de Marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création en gestion de marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione vendite.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">マーケティング管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Управление маркетингом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การสร้างการทำงานในการจัดการการตลาด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">市场管理中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">行銷管理中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MARKETING_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Marketing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Administrador de Marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression en gestion de marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione vendite.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">マーケティング管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Управление маркетингом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การลบการทำงานในการจัดการการตลาด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">市场管理中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">行銷管理中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MARKETING_ROLE_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited update operations in the Marketing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización Limitadas en el Administrador de Marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations d'actualisation limitée en gestion de marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento limitate nella gestione vendite.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">マーケティング管理での限定された更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции ограниченного обновления в приложении Управление маркетингом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการอัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการการตลาด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">市场管理中有限的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">行銷管理中有限的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MARKETING_ROLE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited view operations in the Marketing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización Limitadas en el Administrador de Marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation limitée en gestion de marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione limitate nella gestione vendite.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">マーケティング管理での限定された表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции ограниченного просмотра в приложении Управление маркетингом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการแสดงการทำงานในการจัดการการตลาด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">市场管理中有限的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">行銷管理中有限的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MARKETING_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Marketing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en el Administrador de Marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations d'actualisation en gestion de marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione vendite.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">マーケティング管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Управление маркетингом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การอัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการการตลาด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">市场管理中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">行銷管理中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MARKETING_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Marketing Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Administrador de Marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation en gestion de marketing.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione vendite.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">マーケティング管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление маркетингом.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การแสดงการทำงานในการจัดการการตลาด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">市场管理中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">行銷管理中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MYPORTAL_CUSTOMER">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the customer screens in myportal.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Usare la visualizzazione clienti in myportal.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">私のポータルで顧客画面の使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">我的门户中使用客户页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">我的入口網站中客戶使用者畫面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MYPORTAL_EMPL-NOEML">
        <value xml:lang="en">Usage of the employee screens in myportal: projectmanager and internal notes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Usare la visualizzazione clienti in myportal: gestione progetti e note interne.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">私のポータルで従業員画面の使用。プロジェクト管理および内部連絡。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">我的门户中使用雇员页面：项目管理和内部便笺。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">我的入口網站中員工使用者畫面:專案管理和內部便箋.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.MYPORTAL_EMPLOYEE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the employee screens in myportal.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Usare la visualizzazione impiegati in myportal.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">私のポータルで従業員画面の使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">我的门户中使用雇员页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">我的入口網站中員工使用者畫面。</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.OAGIS_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Oagis application.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nell'applicazione Oagis.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">Oagis業務での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">Oagis应用程序中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">Oagis應用程式中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.OFBTOOLS_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Permission to access the Stock OFBiz Manager Applications.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Permisos para acceder el menú de Herramientas Web.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Autorisation d'accéder aux applications de gestion d'OFBiz existant par défaut.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Permesso per accedere alle applicazione di gestione strumenti OFBiz.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ストックOFBiz管理業務にアクセスする権限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Права доступа к меню Инструменты.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">Permission to access the Stock OFBiz Manager Applications.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">访问库存OFBiz管理程序的权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訪問庫存OFBiz管理程式的權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_4C_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create sales forecasts in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear pronósticos de ventas en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer les prévisions de ventes en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare previsioni di vendita nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での営業予測の作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание прогнозов продаж в Управлении заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการวางแผนการขายในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中创建销售预测。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中新建銷售預測.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_4C_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update sales forecasts in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualizar pronósticos de ventas en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mettre à jour les prévisions de ventes en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare previsioni di vendita nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での営業予測の更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление прогнозов продаж в Управлении заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทการวางแผนการขายในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中更新销售预测。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中更新銷售預測.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES les opérations en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_CRQ_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create Customer Requests in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear Solicitudes de Clientes en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer les demandes de client en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creazioni richieste clienti nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での顧客リクエストの作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание пользовательских запросов в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างคำร้องขอของลูกค้าในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的创建客户请求。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的新建客戶請求.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления  в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_NOTE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create notes in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear Notas en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer les notes en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare note nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での連絡の作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание примечаний в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างข้อความในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的创建便笺。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的新建便箋.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_PURCHASE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create purchase orders in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear órdenes de compra en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer les commandes d'achat en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione ordini di acquisto nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での購買注文の作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание закупочных заказов в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างรายการสั่งซื้อในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的创建采购订单。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的新建採購訂單.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_PURCHASE_ENTRY">
        <value xml:lang="en">Purchase Order Entry in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Entrada de Órdenes de Compra en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Saisie de commande d'achat en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di inserimento ordini di acquisto nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での購買注文エントリ。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ввод закупочного заказа в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การเข้าสู่รายการสั่งซื้อในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的采购订单记录。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的採購訂單記錄.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_PURCHASE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View purchase orders in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Ver órdenes de compra en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Visualiser les commandes d'achat en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione ordini di acquisto nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での購買注文の表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Просмотр закупочных заказов в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงรายการสั่งซื้อในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中浏览采购订单。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中檢視採購訂單.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_QUOTE_PRICE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Quote price manager in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Administrar de precios de Cotizaciones en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Gestion des prix des devis en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Gestione prezzi preventivi nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での見積価格管理。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Менеджер ценовых предложений в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การจัดการการแจ้งราคาในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的询价管理。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的詢價管理.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_RETURN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Process returns in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Procesar Devoluciones en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Traiter les retours en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Avanzamento resi ordini nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での返品の処理。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обработка возвратов в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ดำเนินการผลตอบแทนในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的处理退货。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的處理退貨.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_ROLE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Create operations in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación Limitadas en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création limitée en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione limitati nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での限定された作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ограниченные операции создания в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการสร้างการทำงานในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中有限的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中有限的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_ROLE_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Delete operations in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación Limitadas en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression limitée en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione limitati nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での限定された削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ограниченные операции удаления в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการลบการทำงานในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中有限的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中有限的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_ROLE_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Update operations in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización Limitadas en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de mise à jour limitée en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento limitati nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での限定された更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ограниченные операции обновления в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการอัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中有限的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中有限的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_ROLE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited view operations in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización Limitadas en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation limitée en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzaione limitati nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での限定された表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ограниченные операции просмотра в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขตการแสดงการทำงานในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中有限的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中有限的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_SALES_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create sales orders for all stores in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear órdenes de venta para todas las tiendas en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer des commandes de vente pour tous les centres de profit en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creazionei ordini di vendita per tutti i negozi nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理でのすべての店舗に対する販売注文の作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание сбытовых заказов для всех торговых точек в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างรายการขายสำหรับคลังทั้งหมดในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中为全部店铺创建销售订单。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中為全部商店新建銷售訂單.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_SALES_ENTRY">
        <value xml:lang="en">Sales Order Entry in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Entrada de Órdenes de Venta en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Saisie de commande de vente en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Inserimento ordini di vendita nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での販売注文エントリ。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Ввод сбытьвого заказа в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การเข้าสู่รายการขายในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的销售订单记录。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的銷售訂單記錄.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_SALES_PRICEMOD">
        <value xml:lang="en">Price change permission for sales orders.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Permisos de cambio de precios para órdenes de venta.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Autorisation de changer le prix pour des commandes de vente</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Permesso di cambio prezzo per ordini di vendita.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">販売注文に対する価格変更権限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Права на изменение цены в сбытовых заказах.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การอนุญาตการเปลี่ยนแปลงราคาสำหรับรายการขาย</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">销售订单的价格变更权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">銷售訂單的價格變更權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_SALES_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update sales orders for all stores in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Permesso di aggiornamento ordini di vendita per tutti i negozi della gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理でのすべての店舗に対する販売注文の更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中为全部店铺更新销售订单。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中為全部商店更新銷售訂單.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_SEND_CONFIRMATION">
        <value xml:lang="en">Send order confirmation notification.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Enviar notificación de confirmación de órden.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Envoyer une notification de confirmation de commande</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Inviare notifica conferma ordine.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文確認通知の送信。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Рассылка уведомлений подтверждающих статус заказа.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ส่งการแจ้งการยืนยันรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">发送订单确认通知。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">發送訂單確認通知.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de mise à jour en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.ORDERMGR_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Order Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Administrador de Órdenes.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opération de visualisation en gestion de commandes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione ordini.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">注文管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление заказами.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงการทำงานในการจัดการรายการสั่งซื้อสินค้า</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">订单管理中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訂單管理中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES les opérations en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление участниками</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_CME-EMAIL_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Can create Email communication events for logged-in user.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Può creare eventi comunicazione email per l'utente autenticato.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ログインユーザに対するEメール通信イベントが作成可能。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">能为已登录用户创建电子邮件沟通事件。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">能為已登入使用者新建電子郵件通訊事件.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_CME-EMAIL_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Can delete Email communication events for logged-in user.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Può cancellare eventi comunicazione email per l'utente autenticato.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ログインユーザに対するEメール通信イベントが削除可能。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">能为已登录用户删除电子邮件沟通事件。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">能為已登入使用者刪除電子郵件通訊事件.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_CME-EMAIL_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Can update Email communication events for logged-in user.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Può aggiornare eventi comunicazione email per l'utente autenticato.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ログインユーザに対するEメール通信イベントが更新可能。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">能为已登录用户更新电子邮件沟通事件。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">能為已登入使用者更新電子郵件通訊事件.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_CME-NOTE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Can create Internal note communication event for logged-in user.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Può creare note interne eventi comunicazione per l'utente autenticato.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ログインユーザに対する内部連絡通信イベントが作成可能。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">能为已登录用户创建内部便笺沟通事件。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">能為已登入使用者新建內部便箋通訊事件.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_CME_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create communication event.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear eventos de comunicación.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer l'évènement de communication</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare eventi comunicazione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">通信イベントの作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание события связи.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างเหตุการณ์ในการติดต่อสื่อสาร</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">创建沟通事件。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">新建通訊事件.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_CME_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete communication event.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Eliminar eventos de comunicación.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Supprimer l'évènement de communication</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Cancellazione eventi comunicazione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">通信イベントの削除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Удаление события связи.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบเหตุการณ์ในการติดต่อสื่อสาร</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">删除沟通事件。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">刪除通訊事件.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_CME_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update communication event.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualizar eventos de comunicación.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mettre à jour l'évènement de communication</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare eventi comunicazione.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">通信イベントの更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление события связи.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทเหตุการณ์ในการติดต่อสื่อสาร</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">更新沟通事件。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">更新通訊事件.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_GRP_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update PartyGroup or Person detail information.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualizar información detallada de Grupo de Entidad o Persona.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mettre à jour l'information détaillée des groupes d'acteurs ou de personnes</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先グループまたは個人詳細情報の更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление подробной информации о групповом участнике и персоне.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทกลุ่มผู้ใช้หรือข้อมูลรายละเอียดบุคคล</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">更新会员组或人员详细信息。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">更新團體群組或人員詳細資訊.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_NOTE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create notes in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear notas en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer les notes en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare note nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での連絡の作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание примечаний в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างขัอความในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中创建便笺。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中新建便箋.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_PCM_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create party contact mechs in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear mecanismos de contacto en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer des coordonnées en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare contatti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先連絡方法の作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание контактного механизма участника в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างวิธีการติดต่อกลุ่มผู้ใช้ในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中创建会员联系方法。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中新建團體聯絡方法.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_PCM_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete party contact mechs in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Eliminar mecanismos de contacto en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Supprimer des coordonnées en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Cancellare contatti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先連絡方法の削除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Удаление контактного механизма участника в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบวิธีการติดต่อกลุ่มผู้ใช้ในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中删除会员联系方法。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中刪除團體聯絡方法.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_PCM_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update party contact mechs in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualizar mecanismos de contacto en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mise en jour de coordonnées en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare contatti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先連絡方法の更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление контактного механизма участника в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทวิธีการติดต่อกลุ่มผู้ใช้ในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中更新会员联系方法。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中更新團體聯絡方法.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_QAL_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create party quals in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear calificaciones en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer des qualifications d'acteur en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare qualificazione soggetti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先資格の作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание свойств участника в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างกลุ่มผู้ใช้เท่าเทียมกันในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中创建会员资格。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中新建團體資格.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_QAL_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete party quals in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Eliminar calificaciones en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Supprimer des qualifications d'acteur en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Eliminare qualificazione soggetti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先資格の削除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Удаление свойств участника в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบกลุ่มผู้ใช้เท่าเทียมกันในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中删除会员资格。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中刪除團體資格.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_QAL_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update party quals in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualizar calificaciones en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mise en jour de qualifications d'acteur en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare qualificazione soggetti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先資格の更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление свойств участника в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทกลุ่มผู้ใช้เท่าเทียมกันในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中更新会员资格。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中更新團體資格.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_REL_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create party relationships in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear relaciones en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer des relations entre acteurs en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare rapporti soggetti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先関係の作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание отношений в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างความสัมพันธ์ของกลุ่มผู้ใช้ในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中创建会员关系。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中新建團體關連.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_REL_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete party relationships in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Eliminar relaciones en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Supprimer des relations entre acteurs en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Cancellare rapporti soggetti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先関係の削除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Удаление отношений в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบความสัมพันธ์ของกลุ่มผู้ใช้ในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中删除会员关系。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中刪除團體關連.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_REL_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update party relationships in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualizar relaciones en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mettre à jour des relations entre acteurs en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare rapporti soggetti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先関係の更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление отношений в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทความสัมพันธ์ของกลุ่มผู้ใช้ในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中更新会员关系。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中更新團體關連.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_ROLE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create party roles in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear roles en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer des rôles d'acteur en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare ruoli soggetti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先ロールの作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание ролей в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างสถานะของกลุ่มผู้ใช้ในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中创建会员角色。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中新建團體角色.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_ROLE_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete party roles in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Eliminar roles en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Supprimer des rôles d'acteur en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Cancellare ruoli soggetti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先ロールの削除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Удаление ролей в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบสถานะของกลุ่มผู้ใช้ในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中删除会员角色。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中刪除團體角色.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_SRC_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create party to data source relations.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear relaciones de orígen entidad a dato.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer des relations de source de données à acteur</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare rapporti sorgenti dati soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">データソース関係に取引先の作成</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание отношений участника и источника данных.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างกลุ่มผู้ใช้ถึงความสัมพันธ์ของแหล่งข้อมูล</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">创建会员到数据源的关系。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">新建團體到資料源的關連.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_STS_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update party status in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualizar estados en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mettre à jour des statuts d'acteur en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare stato soggetti nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での取引先ステータスの更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление статуса участника в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทสถานะของกลุ่มผู้ใช้ในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中更新会员状态。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中更新團體狀態.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de mise à jour des en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazione di aggiornamento nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PARTYMGR_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Party Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Administrador de Entidades.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation en gestion d'acteurs</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazione di visualizzazione nella gestione soggetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление участниками.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงการทำงานในการจัดการกลุ่มผู้ใช้</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">会员管理中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">團體管理中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PAYPROC_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Payment Processors Setup.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Procesador de Pagos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES les opérations dans l'organisation des processeurs de paiement</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella configurazione processori pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">取引先管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Настройка платежных процессоров.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการติดตั้งหน่วยประมวลผลกลางการชำระเงิน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">支付处理程序设置中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">付款處理程式設置中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PAYPROC_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Payment Processors Setup.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Procesador de Pagos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création l'organisation des processeurs de paiement</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella configurazione processori pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">支払プロセッサ設定での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Настройка платежных процессоров.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในการติดตั้งหน่วยประมวลผลกลางการชำระเงิน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">支付处理程序设置中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">付款處理程式設置中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PAYPROC_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Payment Processors Setup.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Procesador de Pagos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression dans l'organisation des processeurs de paiement</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella configurazione processori pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">支払プロセッサ設定での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Настройка платежных процессоров.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในการติดตั้งหน่วยประมวลผลกลางการชำระเงิน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">支付处理程序设置中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">付款處理程式設置中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PAYPROC_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Payment Processors Setup.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Procesador de Pagos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation dans l'organisation des processeurs de paiement</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella configurazione processori pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">支払プロセッサ設定での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Настройка платежных процессоров.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงการทำงานในการติดตั้งหน่วยประมวลผลกลางการชำระเงิน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">支付处理程序设置中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">付款處理程式設置中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PAY_INFO_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL Payment Information Operations.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las Operaciones de Información de Pagos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES les opérations d'information de paiement</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni sulle informazioni pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">すべての支払情報操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции связанные с платежной информацией.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานข้อมูลการชำระเงินทั้งหมด</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">全部支付信息操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">全部付款資訊操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PAY_INFO_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create Payment Information.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Crear Información de Pagos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Créer l'information de paiement</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare informazioni pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">支払情報の作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Создание платежной информации.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างข้อมูลการชำระเงิน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">创建支付信息。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">新建付款資訊.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PAY_INFO_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete Payment Information.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Eliminar Información de Pagos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Supprimer l'information de paiement</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Cancellare informazioni pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">支払情報の削除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Удаление платежной информации.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบข้อมูลการชำระเงิน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">删除支付信息。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">刪除付款資訊.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PAY_INFO_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update Payment Information.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Actualizar Información de Pagos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Mettre à jour l'information de paiement</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare informazioni pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">支払情報の更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Обновление платежной информации.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทข้อมูลการชำระเงิน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">更新支付信息。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">更新付款資訊.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PAY_INFO_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View Payment Information.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Ver Información de Pagos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Visualiser l'information de paiement</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Visualizzare informazioni pagamenti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">支払情報の表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Просмотр платежной информации.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงข้อมูลการชำระเงิน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">浏览支付信息。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視付款資訊.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PERIOD_MAINT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the Period Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Usar las páginas de Mantenimiento de Períodos.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Utiliser les pages de gestion des périodes de temps</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Usare le pagine di manutenzione periodi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">期間管理ページの使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Использование страниц Обслуживание периода.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ใช้หน้าการรักษาช่วงเวลา</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">使用阶段维护页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">使用階段維護頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Project Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella gestione progetti.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">プロジェクト管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">项目管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">專案管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_ROLE_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">All admin operations in the Project Manager for a project/phase/task the user is member of.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni di amministrazione nella gestione progetti per un progetto/fase/compito di cui l'utente è membro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ユーザがメンバになっているプロジェクト/フェーズ/タスクに対するプロジェクト管理でのすべての管理操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">项目管理中的全部管理操作，用于用户作为成员的项目/阶段/任务。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">專案管理中的全部管理操作,用於使用者作為成員的專案/階段/任務.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_ROLE_TASK_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Be able to create a task (should be member of project)</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Essere autorizzato a creare un compito (dovrebbe essere membro del progetto)</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">タスクの作成が可能 (プロジェクトのメンバであること)</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">能够创建任务(应该是项目成员)</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">能夠新建任務(應該是專案成員)</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_ROLE_TIMESHEET_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Be able to create a weekly timesheet for the loginid.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Essere autorizzato a creare una timbratura settimanale per l'utente autenticato.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ログインIDに対する週次予定表の作成が可能</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">能够为登录用户创建每周的工时单。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">能夠為登入消費者新建每週的工時單.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_ROLE_TIMESHEET_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Be able to update(report) on an existing own timesheet</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Essere autorizzato ad aggiornare una timbratura esistente</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">既存の自分の予定表の更新(レポート)が可能</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">能够对一个已存在的自己的工时单进行更新(报告)</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">能夠對一個已存在的自己的工時單進行更新(報告)</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_ROLE_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Project Manager for a project/phase/task the user is member of.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione progetti per un progetto/fase/compito ci cui l'utente è membro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ユーザがメンバになっているプロジェクト/フェーズ/タスクに対するプロジェクト管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">项目管理中的更新操作，用于用户作为成员的项目/阶段/任务。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">專案管理中的更新操作,用於使用者作為成員的專案/階段/任務.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_ROLE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">All view operations in the Project Manager for a project/phase/task the user is member of..</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le perazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione progetti per un progetto/fase/compito ci cui l'utente è membro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ユーザがメンバになっているプロジェクト/フェーズ/タスクに対するプロジェクト管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">项目管理中的全部浏览操作，用于用户作为成员的项目/阶段/任务。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">專案管理中的全部檢視操作,用於使用者作為成員的專案/階段/任務.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_TIMESHEET_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Be able to create any weekly timesheet.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Essere autorizzato a creare qualiasi timbratura settimanale.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">任意の週次予定表の作成が可能</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">能够创建任一周工时单。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">能夠新建任一週工時單.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_TIMESHEET_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Be able to update any weekly timesheet.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Essere autorizzato ad aggiornare qualiasi timbratura settimanale.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">任意の週次予定表の更新が可能</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">能够更新任一周工时单。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">能夠更新任一週工時單.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.PROJECTMGR_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL View operations in the Project Manager(but can be limited by ROLE_VIEW)</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione progetti (ma può essere limitato a ROLE_VIEW)</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">プロジェクト管理でのすべての表示操作 (ROLE_VIEWに限り)</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">项目管理中的全部浏览操作(能够被ROLE_VIEW限制)</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">專案管理中的全部檢視操作(能夠被ROLE_VIEW限制)</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.SECURITY_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Security Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en las pantallas de Administración de Seguridad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES les opérations dans les écrans de gestion de sécurité</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella gestione della sicurezza.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">セキュリティ管理画面でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Управление безопасностью.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในหน้าจอการจัดการความปลอดภัย</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在安全管理页面中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在安全管理畫面中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.SECURITY_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Security Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en las pantallas de Administración de Seguridad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création les dans les écrans de gestion de sécurité</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione della sicurezza.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">セキュリティ管理画面での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Управление безопасностью.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในหน้าจอการจัดการความปลอดภัย</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在安全管理页面中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在安全管理畫面中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.SECURITY_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Security Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en las pantallas de Administración de Seguridad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression dans les écrans de gestion de sécurité</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione della sicurezza.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">セキュリティ管理画面での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Управление безопасностью.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในหน้าจอการจัดการความปลอดภัย</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在安全管理页面中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在安全管理畫面中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.SECURITY_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Security Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en las pantallas de Administración de Seguridad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de mise à jour dans les écrans de gestion de sécurité</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione della sicurezza.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">セキュリティ管理画面での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Управление безопасностью.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทการทำงานในหน้าจอการจัดการความปลอดภัย</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在安全管理页面中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在安全管理畫面中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.SECURITY_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Security Management Screens.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en las pantallas de Administración de Seguridad.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation dans les écrans de gestion de sécurité</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione della sicurezza.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">セキュリティ管理画面での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Управление безопасностью.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงการทำงานในหน้าจอการจัดการความปลอดภัย</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在安全管理页面中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在安全管理畫面中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.SEND_CONTROL_APPLET">
        <value xml:lang="en">Send to the Control Applet.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Enviar a Applet de Control.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Envoyer à l'applet de contrôle</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Invia all'Applet.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">コントロールアプレットに送信。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Отсылка в контрольный апплет.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">Send to the Control Applet.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">发送到控制小程序。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">發送到控制Applet.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.SERVER_STATS_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View the Server Statistics pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Ver las páginas de Estadísticas del Servidor.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Visualiser les pages de statistiques du serveur</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Mostra pagine statistiche server.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サーバ統計ページの表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Просмотр статистики по работе сервера.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงหน้าจอสถิติผู้ให้บริการ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">浏览服务器统计页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視伺服器統計頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.SERVICE_INVOKE_ANY">
        <value xml:lang="en">Permission to invoke any service remotely.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Permisos para invocar remotamente cualquier servicio.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Autorisation pour appeler tout service à distance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Permessi di invocare qualsiasi servizio remotamente.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">任意のリモートサービスを呼び出す権限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Права за удаленное выполнение любой службы.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การอนุญาตถึงการร้องขอบริการเล็กน้อยบางอย่าง</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">远程调用任何服务的权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">遠端呼叫任何服務的權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.SERVICE_MAINT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the Service Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Usar las páginas de Mantenimiento de Servicios.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Utiliser les pages du service de maintenance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Usare le pagine di manutenzione servizi.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">サーバ管理ページの使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Использование страниц приложения Обслуживание служб.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ใช้หน้าการรักษาสภาพการบริการ</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">使用服务维护页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">使用服務維護頁面.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.TAXRATE_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Tax Rate Editor.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las Operaciones el Editor de Tasas Impositivas.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES les opérations dans l'éditeur de taux d'expédition.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nelle percentuali delle tasse.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">税率エディタでのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в Редакторе налоговых ставок.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการแก้ไขอัตราภาษี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在税率编辑器中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在稅率編輯器中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.TAXRATE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Tax Rate Editor.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación el Editor de Tasas Impositivas.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création dans l'éditeur de taux de taxe.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nelle percentuali delle tasse.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">税率エディタでの作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в Редакторе налоговых ставок.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในการแก้ไขอัตราภาษี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在税率编辑器中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在稅率編輯器中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.TAXRATE_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Tax Rate Editor.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación el Editor de Tasas Impositivas.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression dans l'éditeur de taux de taxe.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nelle percentuali delle tasse.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">税率エディタでの削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в Редакторе налоговых ставок.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในการแก้ไขอัตราภาษี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在税率编辑器中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在稅率編輯器中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.TAXRATE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Tax Rate Editor.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización el Editor de Tasas Impositivas.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation dans l'éditeur de taux de taxe.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nelle percentuali delle tasse.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">税率エディタでの表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в Редакторе налоговых ставок.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงการทำงานในการแก้ไขอัตราภาษี</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">在税率编辑器中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">在稅率編輯器中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.TEMPEXPR_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">Temporal expression admin</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Amministrazione espressioni temporali</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">時間表現管理</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">时间表达式管理</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">時間運算式管理</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.USERPREF_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">User preferences admin</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Amministrazione preferenze utente</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ユーザ設定管理</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">用户设置管理</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">使用者設定管理</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.UTIL_CACHE_EDIT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Edit a UtilCache instance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Editar una instancia de UtilCache.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Modifier une instance de cache.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare una instanza della cache.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">キャッシュユーティリティインスタンスの編集。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Изменение экземпляра UtilCache.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">Edit a UtilCache instance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">编辑一个应用缓存实例。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">編輯一個應用快取實例.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.UTIL_CACHE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View a UtilCache instance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Ver una instancia de UtilCache.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Visualiser une instance de cache.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Visualizzare una instanza della cache.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">キャッシュユーティリティインスタンスの表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Просмотр экземпляра UtilCache.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">View a UtilCache instance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">浏览一个应用缓存实例。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視一個應用快取實例.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.UTIL_DEBUG_EDIT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Edit a UtilDebug instance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Editar una instancia de UtilDebug</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Modifier une instance de débogage.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiornare una instanza di debug.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">デバッグユーティリティインスタンスの編集。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Изменение экземпляра UtilDebug.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">Edit a UtilDebug instance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">编辑一个应用调试实例。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">編輯一個應用調試實例.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.UTIL_DEBUG_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View a UtilDebug instance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Ver una instancia de UtilDebug</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Visualiser une instance de débogage.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Visualizzzare una instanza di debug.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">デバッグユーティリティインスタンスの表示。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Просмотр экземпляра UtilDebug.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">View a UtilDebug instance.</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">浏览一个应用调试实例。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視一個UtilDebug實例.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.VISUALTHEME_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations on Visual Themes and Visual Theme Resources.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni sui temi visuali e risorse dei temi visuali</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">外観のテーマおよび外観のテーマリソースのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">视觉风格和视觉风格资源的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">視覺風格和視覺風格資源的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.VISUALTHEME_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create Visual Themes and Visual Theme Resources.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Creare temi visuali e risorse dei temi visuali</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">外観のテーマおよび外観のテーマリソースの作成。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">创建视觉风格和视觉风格资源。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">新建視覺風格和視覺風格資源.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.VISUALTHEME_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete Visual Themes and Visual Theme Resources.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Cancella temi visuali e risorse dei temi visuali</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">外観のテーマおよび外観のテーマリソースの削除。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">删除视觉风格和视觉风格资源。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">刪除視覺風格和視覺風格資源.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.VISUALTHEME_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update Visual Themes and Visual Theme Resources.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Aggiorna temi visuali e risorse dei temi visuali</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">外観のテーマおよび外観のテーマリソースの更新。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">更新视觉风格和视觉风格资源。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">更新視覺風格和視覺風格資源.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WEBTOOLS_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Permission to access the WebTools Menu.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Permisos para acceder el menú de Herramientas Web.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Autorisation pour accèder au menu Adm. Sys.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Permessi di accedere ai menu strumenti web.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">Webツールメニューにアクセスする権限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Права на доступ к меню Инструменты.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การอนุญาตถึงสิทธ์ในการเข้าเมนูเว็บทูล</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">访问Web工具菜单的权限。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">訪問Web工具功能表的權限.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKEFFORTMGR_ADMIN">
        <value xml:lang="en">ALL operations in the Work Effort Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">TODAS las operaciones en el Administrador de Esfuerzos de Trabajo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">TOUTES opérations en gestion de tâche.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tutte le operazioni nella gestione impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果管理でのすべての操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Все операции в приложении Организатор.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทำงานทั้งหมดในการจัดการความพยายามในการทำงาน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务管理中的全部操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入服務管理中的全部操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKEFFORTMGR_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Create operations in the Work Effort Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Creación en el Administrador de Esfuerzos de Trabajo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de création en gestion de tâche.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di creazione nella gestione impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果管理での作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции создания в приложении Организатор.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างการทำงานในการจัดการความพยายามในการทำงาน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务管理中的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入服務管理中的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKEFFORTMGR_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Delete operations in the Work Effort Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Eliminación en el Administrador de Esfuerzos de Trabajo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de suppression en gestion de tâche.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di cancellazione nella gestione impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果管理での削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции удаления в приложении Организатор.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ลบการทำงานในการจัดการความพยายามในการทำงาน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务管理中的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入服務管理中的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKEFFORTMGR_ROLE_CREATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Create operations in the Work Effort Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni limitate in creazione nelle gestione impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果管理での限定された作成操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务管理中有限的创建操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入服務管理中有限的新建操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKEFFORTMGR_ROLE_DELETE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Delete operations the Work Effort Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni limitate in cancellazione nelle gestione impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果管理での限定された削除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务管理中有限的删除操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入管理中有限的刪除操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKEFFORTMGR_ROLE_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited Update operations in the Work Effort Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni limitate in aggiornamento nelle gestione impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果管理での限定された更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务管理中有限的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入服務管理中有限的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKEFFORTMGR_ROLE_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">Limited View operations in the Work Effort Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni limitate in visualizzazione nelle gestione impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果管理での限定された表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务管理中有限的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入服務管理中有限的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKEFFORTMGR_UPDATE">
        <value xml:lang="en">Update operations in the Work Effort Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Actualización en el Administrador de Esfuerzos de Trabajo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de mise à jour en gestion de tâche.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di aggiornamento nella gestione impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果管理での更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции обновления в приложении Организатор.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อัพเดทการทำงานในการจัดการความพยายามในการทำงาน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务管理中的更新操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入服務管理中的更新操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKEFFORTMGR_VIEW">
        <value xml:lang="en">View operations in the Work Effort Manager.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Operaciones de Visualización en el Administrador de Esfuerzos de Trabajo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Opérations de visualisation en gestion de tâche.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Operazioni di visualizzazione nella gestione impegni di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">作業成果管理での表示操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Операции просмотра в приложении Организатор.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แสดงการทำงานในการจัดการความพยายามในการทำงาน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">人工服务管理中的浏览操作。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">工作投入服務管理中的檢視操作.</value>
    </property>
    <property key="SecurityPermission.description.WORKFLOW_MAINT">
        <value xml:lang="en">Use the Workflow Maintenance pages.</value>
        <value xml:lang="es">Usar las páginas de Mantenimiento de Flujo de Trabajo.</value>
        <value xml:lang="fr">Utiliser les pages d'entretien du Workflow.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Usare le pagine di gestion flussi di lavoro.</value>
        <value xml:lang="ja">ワークフロー管理ページの使用。</value>
        <value xml:lang="ru">Использование приложения Обслуживание процессов(WF).</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ใช้หน้าการรักษาสภาพขั้นตอนการทำงาน</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh">使用工作流维护页面。</value>
        <value xml:lang="zh-TW">使用工作流程維護頁面.</value>
    </property>
</resource>
