<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!--
    Licensed to the Apache Software Foundation (ASF) under one
    or more contributor license agreements.  See the NOTICE file
    distributed with this work for additional information
    regarding copyright ownership.  The ASF licenses this file
    to you under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the
    "License"); you may not use this file except in compliance
    with the License.  You may obtain a copy of the License at
    
    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
    
    Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing,
    software distributed under the License is distributed on an
    "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY
    KIND, either express or implied.  See the License for the
    specific language governing permissions and limitations
    under the License.
-->
<resource xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceApplication">
        <value xml:lang="en">Business Intelligence Application</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Applicazione Business Intelligence</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">โปรแกรมประยุกต์การเรียนรู้ทางธุรกิจ</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceCompanyName">
        <value xml:lang="en">OFBiz: Business Intelligence</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">OFBiz: Business Intelligence</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">OFBiz:การเรียนรู้ทางธุรกิจ</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceCompanySubtitle">
        <value xml:lang="en">Part of the Open For Business Family of Open Source Software</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Part of the Open For Business Family of Open Source Software</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ส่วนหนึ่งของธุรกิจแบบครอบครัวที่เป็นซอฟต์แวร์โอเพนซอส</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceCurrentStatus">
        <value xml:lang="en">Current Status</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Stato Attuale</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สถานะในปัจจุบัน</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceFieldDescription">
        <value xml:lang="en">Field Description</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Descrizione Campo</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">รายละเอียดข้อมูล</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceFieldName">
        <value xml:lang="en">Field Name</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Nome Campo</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ชื่อข้อมูล</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceIntegratedFramework">
        <value xml:lang="en">Business Intelligence Integrated Framework</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Business Intelligence Framework Integrato</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">Framework ของการเรียนรู้ทางธุรกิจรวมกัน</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceMainPage">
        <value xml:lang="en">Main Page</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Pagina Principale</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">หน้าหลัก</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote1">
        <value xml:lang="en">This is a proof of concept for an OFBiz integrated framework for business intelligence analysis.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Questo è un prototipo per un OFBiz framework integrato per analisi di business intelligence.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การทดสอบความเข้าใจสำหรับ OFBiz framework เพื่อการวิเคราะห์ระบบการเรียนรู้ทางธุรกิจ</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote10">
        <value xml:lang="en">The best practices for datawarehouses are mainly taken from the great book "The Data Warehouse Toolkit - Second Edition" by Ralph Kimball.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Le migliori pratiche per i datawarehouses sono stati ricavati dal grande libro "The Data Warehouse Toolkit - Second Edition" di Ralph Kimball.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">วิธีปฏิบัติที่ดีที่สุดสำหรับข้อมูลคลังสินค้าส่วนใหญ่มาจากหนังสือดี ๆ ชื่อ "The Data Warehouse Toolkit - Second Edition" โดย Ralph Kimball</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote11">
        <value xml:lang="en">The data for dimensions and facts are maintained and kept up to date using standard OFBiz services</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">I dati per dimensioni e fatti sono manutenibili e mantenuti aggiornati usando gli standard dei servizi OFBiz</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ข้อมูลสำหรับขอบเขตและข้อเท็จจริงคือการดูแลและรักษาวันที่ใช้บริการ OFBiz</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote12">
        <value xml:lang="en">(most of them written in minilang to facilitate customizations) and eca rules (easily customizable).</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">(molti dei quali sono scritti utizzando minilang per facilitare le personalizzazioni) e le regole eca (facilmente personalizzabili).</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">(สิ่งที่เขียนทั้งมหดใน minilang ถึง facilitate customizations) และเข้าแทนที่สถานะ (อย่างสะดวก)</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote13">
        <value xml:lang="en">The main low level services to post data to the datawarehouse,</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">I servizi principali a basso livello per ricavare i dati del datawarehouse,</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">หลักการบริการระดับล่างในการบันทึกข้อมูลลงในคลังข้อมูลสินค้า</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote14">
        <value xml:lang="en">to map the operational keys with the datawarehouse ones, and to manage</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">la mappa di chiavi operazionali con il datawarehouse, e la gestione</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แผนที่สำคัญที่สามารถใช้งานได้ด้วยข้อมูลคลังสินค้าและการจัดการ</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote15">
        <value xml:lang="en">history of data changes are already implemented; they will be improved as the datawarehouse will grow (e.g. performance enhancements).</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">storia di cambio di dati che sono già implementati; sarà aumentato di caratteristiche non appena crescerà il datawarehouse (e.g. aumento prestazioni).</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ความเป็นมาของข้อมูลได้เปลี่ยนแปลงเรียบร้อยแล้ว; ได้มีการปรับปรุงข้อมูลคลังสินค้าให้ดีขึ้น (ตัวอย่างเช่น การทำให้ดีขึ้น)</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote16">
        <value xml:lang="en">The following dimensions (and data services) are defined: CurrencyDimension, DateDimension, ProductDimension;</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Le seguenti dimensioni (e servizi dei dati) sono definiti: CurrencyDimension, DateDimension, ProductDimension;</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การวัดขนาดตามที่กำหนด (และข้อมูลการบริการ) ระบุ : CurrencyDimension, DateDimension, ProductDimension;</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote17">
        <value xml:lang="en">we will have to complete them and design the other ones (the total number of dimension will be probably around 20).</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">verranno usati per completare questi e disegnare gli altri (il numero totale di dimensioni saranno probabilmente circa 20).</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">เรากำลังทำสิ่งเหล่านั้นสำเร็จแล้วและวางแผนสิ่งต่อไป (จำนวนทั้งหมดประมาณ 20)</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote18">
        <value xml:lang="en">Just one fact and one star schema are defined: SalesInvoiceItemFact and SalesInvoiceItemStarSchema.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Solo un fatto e uno star schema sono definiti: SalesInvoiceItemFact e SalesInvoiceItemStarSchema.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">จะต้องระบุ 1 ข้อเท็จจริงและ 1 โครงการ: SalesInvoiceItemFact and SalesInvoiceItemStarSchema</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote19">
        <value xml:lang="en">You can quickly initialize the datawarehouse by clicking on the link below:</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Tu puoi velocemente inizializzare il datawarehouse facendo click sul link qui sotto:</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">คุณสามารถเริ่มต้นเข้าสู่ข้อมูลคลังสินค้าได้อย่างรวดเร็วโดยการคลิกบนลิงค์ด้านล่างนี้</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote2">
        <value xml:lang="en">The idea is to define a set entities for business intelligence analysis in a separate (olap) database,</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">L'idea è di definire un'insieme di entità per le analisi di business intelligence in un database (olap) separato,</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">แผนการในการตั้งค่าสิ่งที่มีอยู่เพื่อวิเคราะห์การเรียนรู้ทางธุรกิจในการแยก (olap) ฐานข้อมูล</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote20">
        <value xml:lang="en">The CurrencyDimension, DateDimension, ProductDimension and the SalesInvoiceItemFact entities will be automatically populated.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Le entità CurrencyDimension, DateDimension, ProductDimension e SalesInvoiceItemFact saranno caricate automaticamente.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">CurrencyDimension, DateDimension, ProductDimension และ SalesInvoiceItemFact จะคงอยู่โดยอัตโนมัติ</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote21">
        <value xml:lang="en">Then you can run the analysis using the report builder menu.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Dopo tu puoi eseguire analisi usando il menu costruzione report.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">หลังจากที่คุณทำการวิเคราะห์แล้วสามารถใช้เมนูการสร้างรายงานได้</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote22">
        <value xml:lang="en">The report builder is a very simple tool that allows you to run</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">La costruzione report è un vero strumento semplice che ti permette di eseguire</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การสร้างรายงานเป็นเครื่องมือง่าย ๆ ที่ให้คุณใช้งานได้</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote23">
        <value xml:lang="en">the analysis on all the star schemas defined in the system.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">le analisi su tutti i star schemas definiti nel sistema.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การวิเคราะห์บนแผนผังทั้งหมดที่ระบุในระบบ</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote24">
        <value xml:lang="en">However, right now there is just one star schema defined:</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Comunque, fino adesso c'è solo un star schema definito:</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">อย่างไรก็ตาม, ขณะนี้มีแผนผังที่กำหนด:</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote25">
        <value xml:lang="en">SalesInvoiceItemStarSchema that is a simple "profit and loss" (P&amp;L) analysis.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">SalesInvoiceItemStarSchema che è una semplice analisi di "profit and loss" (P&amp;L).</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">SalesInvoiceItemStarSchema เป็นการวิเคราะห์ขั้นพื้นฐานของ "กำไรและขาดทุน" (P&amp;L) </value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote26">
        <value xml:lang="en">Just select using the checkboxes the fields (columns) you want to see in the report</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Appena selezionato i campi dei checkboxes (colonne) tu vorrai vedere</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">จะต้องเลือกใช้เช็คบ็อก (คอลัมภ์) ตามที่คุณต้องการให้มีในรายงาน</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote27">
        <value xml:lang="en">and a simple report will be shown: according to the columns selected the data will be aggregated (drill up/down);</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">e un semplice report verrà mostrato: in accordo alle colonne selezionate i dati verranno aggregati (drill up/down);</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">และพื้นฐานของรายงานจะต้องแสดง: ตามคอลัมภ์ที่เลือกข้อมูลจะต้องรวมกัน (drill up/down);</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote28">
        <value xml:lang="en">all the descriptions you see in the report screens are pulled from the entity definitions.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">tutte le descrizioni che tu vedrai nelle scrermate del report sono prelevare dalla definizioni delle entità.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">รายละเอียดทั้งหมดที่คุณเห็นในหน้ารายงานดึงมาจากสิ่งที่กำหด</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote29">
        <value xml:lang="en">The initialization is needed only once, because the product data and sales invoice data</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">L'inizializzazione è necessaria solo una volta, perchè i dati del prodotti e i dati delle fatture di vendita</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">การเริ่มต้นเป็นความต้องการอย่างแรกเพราะเป็นข้อมูลสินค้าและข้อมูลใบแจ้งการขาย</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote3">
        <value xml:lang="en">accessible, in the same way as the main one (olap), via the delegator.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">accessibile, nello stesso modo di quello principale (oltp), attraverso un delegator.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สามารถเข้าถึงได้ในทางเดียวกันกับทางแรก (oltp)</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote30">
        <value xml:lang="en">are kept updated by ecas: if you create/update a product or create a new invoice,</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">sono mantenute aggiornate dagli ecas: se tu crei/aggiorni un prodotto o creare una nuova fattura,</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">เป็นการเปลี่ยนแปลงโดยการแทนที่: ถ้าคุณสร้าง/เปลี่ยนแปลงสินค้าหรือสร้างใบส่งของใหม่</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote31">
        <value xml:lang="en">the new information will be immediately included in the datawarehouse analysis.</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">la nuova informazione sarà immediatamente inclusa nelle analisi del datawarehouse.</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ข้อมูลใหม่จะต้องรวมทันทีในการวิเคราะห์ข้อมูลคลังสินค้า</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote4">
        <value xml:lang="en">The new olap database, will contain all the entities necessary to datawarehouse analysis:</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Il nuovo database olap, conterrà tutte le entità necessarie alle analisi di datawarehouse:</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ฐานข้อมูล olap ใหม่จะประกอบด้วยสิ่งที่มีอยู่ซึ่งจำเป็นในการวิเคราะห์ข้อมูลคลังสินค้า:</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote5">
        <value xml:lang="en">dimensions, facts and star schemas (that are view-entities).</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">dimensioni, fatti e star schemas (queste sono view-entities).</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขต,ข้อเท็จจริงและแผนผัง (เป็นการแสดงสิ่งที่มีอยู่)</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote6">
        <value xml:lang="en">The dimensions, facts and star schemas are defined according to best practices for datawarehouses</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Le dimensioni, fatti e star schemas sono definiti in accordo alle migliori pratiche per i datawarehouses</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ขอบเขต,ข้อเท็จจริงและแผนผังตามที่ระบุเป็นวิธีปฏิบัติที่ดีที่สุดสำหรับข้อมูลคลังสินค้า</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote7">
        <value xml:lang="en">and best practices for OFBiz: they are defined as standard entities using the xml entity defs;</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">e le migliori pratiche per OFBiz: queste sono definite come entità standard usando le definizioni xml entity;</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">และวิธีปฏิบัติที่ดีที่สุดสำหรับ OFBiz คือ: ต้องกำหนดมาตรฐานสิ่งที่มีอยู่ให้เหมือนกับที่ใช้ใน xml </value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote8">
        <value xml:lang="en">clear and consistent naming conventions are used and they are documented</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">corretti e consistenti convenzione nei nomi sono usati and sono documentati</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">ยกเลิกและใช้ชื่อข้อตกลงที่สอดคล้องกันและเป็นไปตามเอกสาร</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceNote9">
        <value xml:lang="en">by meta data descriptions (in the entity def).</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">dalle descrizione dei meta dati (nella definizione entità).</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">โดยรายละเอียดที่มาของข้อมูล(อยู่ในที่กำหนด)</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceQuickInitDataWarehouse">
        <value xml:lang="en">Quick Init DataWarehouse</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Inizializzazione Veloce DataWarehouse</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">เริ่มต้นเข้าสู่ข้อมูลคลังสินค้าอย่างรวดเร็ว</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceQuickStartGuide">
        <value xml:lang="en">Quick Start Guide</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Guida Rapida</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">เข้าสู่คำแนะนำอย่างรวดเร็ว</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceRenderTheReport">
        <value xml:lang="en">Render the Report</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Visualizza il Report</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">เสนอรายงาน</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceReportBuilder">
        <value xml:lang="en">Report Builder</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Costruzione Report</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">สร้างรายงาน</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceReportBuilderRenderStarSchemaReport">
        <value xml:lang="en">Render Star Schema Report</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Visualizza Report Star Schema</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">เสนอแผนผังรายงาน</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceReportBuilderSelectStarSchema">
        <value xml:lang="en">Select Star Schema</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Seleziona Star Schema</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">เลือกแผนผัง</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceReportBuilderSelectStarSchemaFields">
        <value xml:lang="en">Select Star Schema Fields</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Seleziona Campi Star Schema</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">เลือกช่องแผนผัง</value>
    </property>
    <property key="BusinessIntelligenceReportBuilderSelectTheStarSchemaReport">
        <value xml:lang="en">Select the start schema (report)</value>
        <value xml:lang="it">Seleziona lo start schema (report)</value>
        <value xml:lang="th">เลือกแผนผัง (รายงาน)</value>
    </property>
</resource>
